Calculate your choices.
The Accountant is a crime, thriller, drama film directed by Gavin O'Connor.
As a math savant uncooks the books for a new client, the Treasury Department
closes in on his activities and the body count starts to rise.
Christian Wolff, played by Ben Affleck.
Marybeth Medina, played by Cynthia Addai-Robinson.
Dana Cummings, played by Anna Kendrick.
Ray King, played by J.K. Simmons.
Brax, played by Jon Bernthal.
Lamar Blackburn, played by John Lithgow.
The Accountant is a 2016 American action thriller film written by Bill Dubuque,
directed by Gavin O'Connor, and starring Ben Affleck, Anna Kendrick, J.
Simmons, Jon Bernthal, Cynthia Addai-Robinson, Jeffrey Tambor, and John Lithgow.
The storyline follows Christian Wolff, an autistic certified public accountant who makes his living sanitizing fraudulent financial and
accounting records of criminal and terrorist organizations around the world that are experiencing internal embezzlement.
The Accountant premiered in Los Angeles on October 10, 2016, and was
theatrically released in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on October 14, 2016.
Receiving mixed reviews from critics, the film grossed $155.2 million worldwide.
It received praise for Affleck's performance and the action sequences featuring the Indonesian
martial art  Pencak Silat, although its portrayal of autism received a mixed response.
A sequel, The Accountant 2, was released in 2025 by Amazon MGM Studios, with Affleck, Bernthal,
Addai-Robinson and Simmons reprising their roles, while a third film is also in development.
The film explores themes of prison, sniper, assassin, autism, military service.
The tone is emotional and intense.